<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ViewDemo_App</string>
    <string name="batmanAndRobinScript">"1	INT. BATCAVE -BATMAN'S COSTUME VAULT

Chrome and shadow.  A black gauntlet SNAPS into place.
A cape WHIPS over a dark rubber back.
A bat-shaped buckle LOCKS.

2	INT. BATCAVE  ROBIN'S COSTUME VAULT - INTERCUT

A silver throwing-bird is chosen from a weapon's array.
Gloved hands lift a black eye mask.  Tunic armor CLICKS shut,
turning to reveal the chest-borne insignia of a Robin.

3	INT.BATCAVE
BATMAN - CLOSE.  Emerges from his costume vault.
WIDER
Deeper excavation has doubled the size of the cavern.

New state-of-the-art computing systems flash.
Surveillance screens monitor news and police FREQUENCIES.
Crime's worst nightmare.

Batman strides towards the rising steam-obscured pedestal
which bears the sleek, redesigned Batmobile.

ROBIN appears in the door of his costume vault, dressed in
the black and red of his Nightwing costume.

Two dark avengers stand suited, ready to take back the night.

		BATMAN
	Nice suit.  And today you are?

		ROBIN
	Nightwing.  Scourge of darkest evil.

		BATMAN
	This is all about fashion for you, isn't it?

		ROBIN
	It's the gear.  Chicks love the gear.

ALFRED steps forward, out of the shadows.

		ALFRED
	Do call if you're going to be late for dinner, sir.


4	TURBOS - CLOSE.  ROAR.  The Batmobile SHOOTS away through
the arches of the cave access tunnel.

5	The compass to of the Batmobile service pedestal splits
wide like the opening petals of a flower, revealing a
sleek, turbo-charged motorcycle.  meet Robin's bike:  The
Redbird.

		ALFRED
	Drive carefully, Master Wing.

		ROBIN
	Don't wait up, AL.

6	The REDBIRD'S TURBO - CLOSE.  EXPLODES into life.
The powerful bike SHOOTS after the Batmobile.

7	ALFRED watches them go.

Then, he relaxes, lets his weight
fall against the main console, a man not as well as he seems.

8	INT. BATCAVE ACCESS TUNNEL - BATMOBILE - MOVING

Batman is behind the wheel, Robin visible through the
window.

		BATMAN
	Ten police cruisers frozen solid on
	the Gotham Expressway . . .

9	INT. BATCAVE ACCESS TUNNEL - REDBIRD - MOVING

Robin is on his bike, data scrolling on his console monitor.

		ROBIN
	... A giant drilling truck burrowing under
	the city ...

		BATMAN
	Mr. Freeze.

		ROBIN
	The batcomputer tracks him heading
	for the Gotham Museum.

		BATMAN
	The new antiquities exhibit.  The
	Second Sun of the Sudan.

		ROBIN
	Of course.  He's going to steal the
	giant white diamond.

		BATMAN
	No, Robin.  He's going to jail.

10	BATMAN'S MONITOR - CLOSE - THE GOTHAM MUSEUM

PUSH IN

11	EXT. GOTHAM MUSEUM - NIGHT

A stone and glass palace set on the edge of Gotham's
Central Park.

12	INT. GOTHAM MUSEUM - NIGHT

A GIANT DRILLING TRUCK points up through the rubble of the
shattered museum floor.

13	WIDER. A great hall bearing the skeleton of a mighty
brontosaur amongst a myriad of other exotic antiquities.
All frozen.

14	HOLD on A GIANT DIAMOND CASE

The case begins to glow blue, then white, the shatterproof
glass EXPLODING into a thousand flying fragments.

15	RACK IN through the storm of ice and glass, ACROSS the
frozen floor, PAST exhibits of Aztec ruins peppered now
with three FROZEN GUARDS, UP stone steps of a pyramid
altar TO REVEAL...
         ...A silver suited figure stands, bald head visible beneath a
helmet,
	A high-tech bazooka in his hand.  MR. FREEZE

		FREEZE
	The Iceman Cometh.

16	WIDER

A gang of Thugs in thermal suits, THE ICEMEN, skate to the
base of the steps.  Two hold a MOANING, shivering GUARD
captive.

		GUARD
	Please.  Show some mercy.

Freeze begins down the altar steps.  A SHIMMERING, TERRIFYING
GOD.

		FREEZE
	I'm afraid my condition has left me
	cold to your pleas of mercy.

17	Freeze FIRES his weapon, the beam of cryonic energy
engulfing the Guard, turning him to ice.

		FREEZE
	(knocks on the guard's cheek)
	Copsicle."</string>
</resources>
